Deliverance In Jesus' Name
He has some powers.
Some powers.
Indonesia Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
I am the servant of lucifer.
The servant of lucifer.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
I know you.
You know me?
Yes.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
No!
I am angry at you.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
You came here to do what?
What is your mission here?
To destroy.
I am a destroyer.
I am destroying humans.
Do you want to fight me?
Yes!
OK. This small boy will fight you. Come here.
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Go! Satan! Go!
This is his son fighting him.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Can you see?
His own son, in the name of Jesus.
So, come on. You are free!
Indonesia Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua
What happened to my father?
OK, father - tell your son what happened to you.
Who are you?
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Stop that nonsense! Come out!
Leave the body!
Do you want to fight me too?
Yes!
I hate you.
What did you say?
She is a legion.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Jesus!
She is free!
Stand up!
I am the king.
OK, it's alright.
Indonesia Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua
You are free.
Congratulations!
Thank You, Jesus.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Hallelujah!
Amen.
Indonesia Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Testimony Time
Let me introduce myself.
My name is Fikri Samosir. I am from North Sumatra in Indonesia.
This is my wife and my two children. I have two boys and one girl.
I would like to testify about what happened that night, September 28.
When I went to the crusade, I was touched by God.
When Prophet T.B. Joshua placed his hand on my head,
I didn’t know what happened after that.
Suddenly, my body was thrown backwards.
I knew that there were seven evil spirits in me.
One of them was called Beelzebub.
Because of the evil spirit in me, there was this hatred and anger
towards the servant of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Do you want to fight me?
Yes.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
I hated him so much and was so angry that I wanted to attack him.
But because of the power of God in Prophet T.B. Joshua, the evil spirit in me had no power.
My body, at that time, was thrown backwards several times, like you can see on the video.
At that time, those seven evil spirits had to leave my body.
Now I am free! Because of the power of God, because God loves me, He did not abandon me;
He did not let those seven spirits to bind me.
I thank the Lord who loves me so much. He has blessed me so much.
I thank His servant, Prophet T.B. Joshua, who is used by the Lord, and for his ministry.
Thank God because my wife, my children and I can be so happy and have such peace,
like nothing I have experienced before. I have never experienced it before -
a freedom that has been given by the Lord Jesus Christ.
And even right now, I have such a joy in my heart tonight that I can stand up here and give testimony.
I have a mission, a plan, a vision - I want to serve God full time because God loves me so much.
I'm going to continue to give my testimony, how much God loves me, how much I love Him.
I love Him so much because of His anointing that flows through me.
And tonight... Thank you so much to the Lord. Thank you so much.
I am not going to stand here any longer
because all of the things I've done in the past, when I was disappointed,
when I was angry, when I hated people - my family, my brother, sister, younger brother,
all those people, but the Lord set me free from that hatred.
Thank You, Lord. Thank You, Jesus. Thank You.
This is my testimony.
Please, pray for me.
Pray for my family, so that we will always be close and intimate with God. Thank you.
Indonesia Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Thank You Lord
You are Holy
Holy Lord and forever You are God
Thank You Lord
You are Holy
Holy Lord and forever You are God
Indonesia Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua
My name is Elisabeth, 52 years old, from Jakarta, Indonesia.
We saw you in the prayer line tonight and we saw Prophet T.B.Joshua coming towards you.
Tell us what happened when you were in the prayer line.
At first, I prayed for my daughter because she had autism.
When the man of God touched me, I felt something hot inside of me.
I felt a war within me that I wanted to hit the man of God. I hated him.
You want to fight me too?
Yes, I hate you.
It made my knees tremble so much that I fell down.
I felt like there was something cold that touched me, when the man of God prayed for me
that made me fall down to the floor.
Yes, it is true.
Indonesia Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Yes, that is right.
When I fell down, I felt like there was something heavy that was removed from my heart.
What I have just said is right.
After the prayer, he said that the evil spirit within me had gone.
Indonesia Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Jesus!
She is free.
After the prayer of Prophet T.B. Joshua, how are you feeling in your body now?
I feel free because something that was in my heart for the past couple of years has gone.
OK, after the prayer of Prophet T.B. Joshua, how are you feeling now?
I got something great and a great independence that I have never had before!
Amen.
We thank God, for what He has done in your life,
and we want to ask you, now that Jesus Christ has delivered you and set you free
through His anointed servant Prophet T.B. Joshua, what is your promise to God?
I will be faithful and serve the Lord, amen!
Her promise is that she will be faithful and serve the Lord. Amen!
Amen. We pray with you that God will give that grace to stay close to Jesus, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV – Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.
RV: Mel Flowers 30/06/2018